# Angela Comes

77 Lake Avenue, Los Angeles, California, 90027 a. cornes@you re m a i I .com (845) 234-8273

Professional and success-oriented makeup artist with six years of experience, including three years self-employed and three years working fora bridal magazine.

Possesses a cosmetology qualification from the American Beauty College School of Cosmetology & Barbering. Proven ability to execute complex makeup looks, makeup prosthetics, special effects makeup, and hairstyles.

Excellent communication skills and ability to build and maintain lasting working relationships.

# Key Skills

- Airbrushing
- Prosthetics
- Special effects makeup
- Impeccable communication and interpersonal skills in-person and via telephone
- Bridal makeup
- Hairstyling
- Knowledge of business marketing
- Computer-literate, including Microsoft Office and Outlook emails

## **Professional Experience**

#### Freelance makeup artist

Self-employed, Los Angeles, CA / May 2018- March 2021

- Provided makeup services for notable TV networks, photographers, fashion designers, and magazines
- Maintained a client satisfaction rate of 99%
- Provided makeup services such as airbrushing, prosthetics, and continuity provision for 20+ cast of a recent feature film
- Maintained a tight schedule
- Provided runway makeup services in a fast-paced environment

#### Makeup artist

Today's Bride San Francisco, San Francisco, CA / November 2015 - May 2018

- Executed bridal makeup and hair looks for more than 10 models per day
- Helped to brainstorm makeup looks with magazine editors and photographers prior to shoots
- Improved the appearance of makeup by introducing new advanced preparation techniques such as exfoliation and extraction
- Maintained excellent customer service manner to maintain positive business relationships

## Education

#### Qualification in Cosmetology

American Beauty College School of Cosmetology & Barbering, West Covina, CA | September 2014 - September 2015

## Certifications

 Certified in Special Effects Makeup by the Cinema Makeup School, April 2018